

Shashank Balodi

Personal Profile

Address

MCF-398, Block Bhagat Singh Colony, Ballabgarh, Faridabad

Phone

+919999795294

Email

balodishashank@gmail.com

Date of Birth 18 July 1992

Languages

English, Hindi

Additional Skills

Sports:

- Volleyball
- American pool
- Table tennis

Others:

- Internet Surfing
- Reading

Professional Summary

Senior UI Developer concentrating in UI development. Experienced with all grades of the development cycle for the dynamic web projects. Well-versed in diverse programming language and frameworks JavaScript, Jquery, Angular. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Work Experience

18/2018- till now

GlobalLogic Pvt. Ltd, Noida

Title: Senior Software Engineer

Client: Odigo

Domain: Contact center as a service

Tools: Javascript, Typescript, Angular, HTML5, CSS3(preprocessor

SASS), Unit Testing(Jasmine/Karma).

Responsibilities:

- Front end team management.
- Requirement gathering from the client.
- Developed UI for creating IVR flows and user data reporting.

02/2017 - 18/2018

HCL Technologies, Noida

Title: Lead Engineer Client: Western Union Domain: Finance

Tools: Javascript, Angular, HTML5, CSS3(preprocessor SASS), CSV,

Jenkins, REST, Perforce.

Responsibilities:

- Front end team management.
- Developed web application for cross border money transfer.

07/2014 - 02/2017

Symfosys Technologies, New Delhi

Title: Senior Software Engineer

Client: Examsoft Domain: Education

Tools: Javascript, JQuery, AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3(preprocessor LESS), Grunt, Gulp, Istanbul, Unit Testing(Jasmine/Karma), JSON, Git,

Bitbucket. Responsibilities:

- Developed UI of the desktop application for online assessments.
- · Client handling and requirement gathering.

Education

2010-2014

BSAITM, Faridabad

B.Tech(Electronics and Communication Engineering)

2008-2010

Bohra Public School, Ballabgarh

10th, 12th(PCM)